<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kaveri Vidya Samsthe</string>
    <string name="Learning_where_Merit_and_Values">KAVERI VIDYA SAMSTHE HS named after Goddess CAUVERY, the Jeevanadi of Karnataka,came into being on the 1st June 1990. Since then, during these thirty three years, the institution has maintained a fruitful relationship with society and other competitive schools. thanks to the noble donors and the patronage of parents.\n\n

"We are committed to build a vibrant,equitable and inclusive environment for staff and students from all walks of life." The school comprises of classes from LKG to X standard and the school has grown from successful academic progress".</string>
    <string name="Foreword_Headmistress">Kavery Vidya Samsthe came into existence in the year 1990, with only Nursery, 1st standard and 8th standard. Since then the school building has grown horizontally and vertically to cater to the needs of the people in and around Mysore city. Now it is a full fledged Institution from LKG to X Standard.The Institution is situated in a serene atmosphere and provides the best learning environment to bring out the innate talents and overlooked creativity of the ‘Cauverians’.</string>
    <string name="Foreword_Administrator">Teaching is a noble profession. An institution works to its fullest for transforming the young minds and nurtures every individual to be a responsible citizen of the country. This is possible with thecommitment and selfless service of the teachers and the management towards providing value based education to the students . Education should not be limited to the boundaries of classroom learning but should spread out from the periphery of the walls towards holistic growth and development</string>
    <string name="history">In this cultural city of Mysore, our prestigious Kaveri Vidya Samsthe HS a dream project of Kodava Samaja, Mysore was established in 1990 to impart quality education to the children of Mysore and Kodagu, has been serving the sacred cause of education for the past 30+ years.</string>
</resources>